{
  "extraDescription": "NB: one operand is in 6-7 and other operand is in 0-7",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 6",
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 6",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 7",
      "answer": "35"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 7",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 7",
      "answer": "28"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 7",
      "answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 3",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 2",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 6",
      "answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 1",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 7",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 6",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 6",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 4",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 6",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 7",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 1",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 3",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 5",
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 7",
      "answer": "49"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 6",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 7",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 2",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 4",
      "answer": "28"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 6",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; 5",
      "answer": "35"
    }
  ]
}
